City of Newburgh Urban Renewal; Collection apap375
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
City of Newburgh Urban Renewal Collection
1935-2000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap375
99.5 cubic ft.
This collection contains materials from the City of Newburgh Engineering Department and the Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency, documenting the City's redevelopment efforts in the mid-late 20th century.
Content Description
This collection contains a variety of materials documenting the City of Newburgh's redevelopment efforts in the mid-late 20th century. These include records from the City of Newburgh Engineering Department and the Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency. The files consist of correspondence, appraisals, deeds, meeting minutes, financials, demolition contracts, and brochures.
Administrative History
During the mid-late 20th century, the City of Newburgh undertook large-scale demolition of approximately 1,300 business and residential structures on historic and commerical city blocks and its waterfront as part of urban renewal efforts. Much of this land then remained undeveloped.
Arrangement of the Collection
This collection is arranged into three series, Administrative, Appraisal, and Engineering Department, which are arranged alphabetically in the finding aid.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
City of Newburgh City Historian Mary McTamaney donated all materials in this collection to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives in 2018.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted with the exception of select files noted in the Administrative series.
Urban renewal -- Newburgh (N.Y.); Architecture; African Americans and Civil Rights Organizations; Neighborhood and Community Associations; Urban development
- Appraisals, 1935-1987; 2; 21 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically with files titled with addresses, parcels, and lot numbers listed first, alphabetically by street.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains appraisal documents of commercial and residential properties in Newburgh from NYR-189 and NYA-10 with full specifications on most of the residential lots (physical condition, measurements, and information on the owners). The documents also include photographs of the properties. A very small number of files related to apprisals are also located in the Administrative series.
  - 1-1-4, 44 Ann Street, Lot 2 (NYR 189), 1966; 1971 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - 1-1-4, 48 Ann Street, Lot 3-4 (NYR 189), 1965-1966; 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - 1-1-4, 50 Ann Street, Lot 5 (NYR 189), 1964-1965; 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 1-1-4, 52 Ann Street, Lot 6 (NYR 189), 1959; 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - 1-1-4, 54 Ann Street & 59-61 Broadway (NYR 189), 1951; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - 1-1-4, 56 Ann Street, Lot 8 (NYR 189), 1957; 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - 1-1-4, 58 Ann Street, Lot 9 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - 1-1-3, 59 Ann Street, Lot 23 (NYR 189), 1960; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 1-1-4, 60 Ann Street, Lot 10 (NYR 189), 1958; 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - 1-1-3, 61 Ann Street, Lot 22 (NYR 189), 1959; 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - 1-1-4, 62-64 Ann Street, Lot 11 (NYR 189), 1958; 1973; 1979 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - 1-1-3, 63 Ann Street, Lot 21 (NYR 189), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 1-1-3, 65 Ann Street, Lot 20 (NYR 189), 1958; 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 1-1-4, 66 Ann Street, Lot 12 (NYR 189), 1961; 1974 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - 1-1-4, 68 Ann Street, Lot 13 (NYR 189), 1958; 1964; 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - 1-1-3, 69-71 Ann Street, Lot 18,19 (NYR 189), 1961; 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 1-1-4, 70 Ann St., Lot 14 (NYR 189), 1946; 1970-1974 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - 4-2-1, 35 Broad St., Lot 26 (NYR 189), 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - 4-2-1, 37 Broad St., Lot 25A (NYR 189), 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - 4-6-2, 55-63 Broad St., Lot 31-33 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 4-6-2, 55-63 Broad St. Rear, Lot 3 (NYR-189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 1-1-4, 43-47 Broadway, Lot 29 (NYR 189), 1970-1974 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - 1-1-4, 49 Broadway, Lot 28 (NYR 189), 1958; 1966; 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - 1-1-4, 51-55 Broadway (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1974; 1975 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - 1-1-4, 57 Broadway, Lot 24 (NYR 189), 1963; 1969; 1971-1975 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - 1-1-4, 63 Broadway, Lot 22 (NYR 189), 1966; 1971-1975 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - 1-1-4, 65-67 Broadway, Lot 21 (NYR 189), 1971-1974 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Block 1-1-4, Parcel 21, 65-67 Broadway, Bet-Ros Realty Corp. (NYR 189), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - 1-1-4, 69 Broadway, Lot 20 (NYR 189), 1945; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - 1-1-4, 71 Broadway, Lot 19 (NYR 189), 1971-1973 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - 1-1-4, 73 Broadway, Lot 18 (NYR 189), 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - 1-1-4, 77-79 Broadway, Lot 15-16 (NYR 189), 1964; 1966; 1973 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - 4-6-2, 50-52 Clinton St., Lot 64 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - 4-6-2, 56 Clinton St., Lot 65-66 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - 4-6-2, 64-68 Clinton St., Lot 68-70 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - 2-1-3, 1 Colden St., Lot 1 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - 2-1-2, 2-4 Colden St., Lot 54 (NYR 189), 1976-1977; Undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - 2-1-3, 3 Colden St., Lot 2-59 (NYR 189), 1969; 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - 2-1-3, 5 Colden St., Lot 3 (NYR 189), 1954; 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - 2-1-2, 6 Colden St., Lot 53 (NYR 189), 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - 2-1-3, 7-9 Colden St., Lot 4 (NYR 189), 1970-1975 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Block 2-1-3, Lot 4, 7-9 Colden Street, Florence DeLong, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - 2-1-2, 8-10 Colden St., Lot 52 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - 2-1-3, 11 Colden St., 12 South Water St. (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Block 2-1-3, Parcel 5 & 56, 11 Colden, Property of Secondiono Risio, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - 2-1-2, 12 Colden St., Lot 51 (NYR 189), 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - 2-1-3, 13 Colden St., Lot 6-55 (NYR 189), 1944; 1970 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - 2-1-2, 14 Colden St., Lot 50 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - 2-1-3, 15 Colden St., 18 South Water St. (NYR 189), 1966; 1970; Undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - 2-1-2, 16 Colden St., Lot 49 (NYR 189), 1965; 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 2-1-3, 17-19 Colden St., Lot 8-9 (NYR 189), 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - 2-1-2, 18 Colden St., Lot 48 (NYR 189), 1969-1972; 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 2-1-2, 20 Colden St., Lot 47 (NYR 189), 1969-1971 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 2-1-3, 21-23 Colden St., Lot 10 (NYR 189), 1970; Undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - 2-1-2, 22 Colden St., Lot 46 (NYR 189), 1954; 1966; 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 2-1-2, 24 Colden St., Lot 45 (NYR 189), 1971-1975 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Block 2-1-2, Parcel 45, 24 Colden St, Frystak Realty Corp, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - 2-1-3, 25 Colden St., Lot 11 (NYR 189), 1949; 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - 2-1-2, 26-28 Colden St., Lot 44 (NYR 189), 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 2-1-3, 27 Colden St., Lot 12 (NYR 189), 1946; 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - 2-1-2, 30 Colden St., Lot 43 (NYR 189), 1944; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 2-1-3, 29 Colden St., Lot 13 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - 2-1-3, 31 Colden St., Lot 14 (NYR 189), 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - 2-1-2, 32 Colden St., Lot 42 (NYR 189), 1949; 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 2-1-3, 33 Colden St., Lot 15 (NYR 189), 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - 2-1-2, 34-36 Colden St., Lot 41 (NYR 189), 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 2-1-3, 35 Colden St., Lot 16 (NYR 189), 1969-1971 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - 2-1-3, 37-39 Colden St., Lot 17,18 (NYR 189), 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - 2-1-2, 38-40 Colden St., Lot 40 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 2-1-2, 42 Colden St., Lot 39 (NYR 189), 1952; 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 2-1-3, 43 Colden St., Lot 19 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 2-1-2, 44 Colden St., Lot 38 (NYR 189), 1946; 1966; 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 2-1-2, 46 Colden St., Lot 37 (NYR 189), 1944; 1956; 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 2-1-3, 47 Colden St., Lot 20 (NYR 189), 1959; 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 2-1-3, 49 Colden St., Lot 21 (NYR 189), 1969; 1970-1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 2-1-3, 51 Colden St., Lot 22, John K. MacMillan (NYR 189), 1969; 1970-1974; 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 2-1-2, 50 Colden St., Lot 35 (NYR 189), 1959; 1966; 1973 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Block 2-1-3, Parcel 22, 51 Colden Street, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - 2-1-2, 52 Colden Street, Lot 34, 1971-1977 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - 2-1-3, 53 Colden St., Lot 23 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 2-1-2, 54 Colden St., Lot 33 (NYR 189), 1959; 1966; 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 2-1-3, 55 Colden St., Lot 24 (NYR 189), 1957; 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 2-1-3, 57-59 Colden Street, Lot 25, 36, 37 (NYR 189), 1969; 1970-1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 2-1-3, 61 Colden St., Lot 26 (NYR 189), 1964; 1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 2-1-2, 62-64 Colden St., Lot 30 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 2-1-3, 63 Colden St., Lot 27 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 2-1-3, 65-67 Colden St., Lot 28-29 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 2-1-2, 66 Colden St., Lot 29 (NYR 189), 1958; 1966-1967; 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 2-1-3, 69 Colden St., Lot 30 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 2-1-2, 60 Colden St., Lot 31 (NYR 189), 1966-1967; 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 2-1-2, 56-58 Colden St., Lot 32 (NYR 189), 1971-1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 2-1-2, 55 First St., Lot 55 (NYR 189), 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - 2-1-1, 73-81 First St., Lot 53 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 2-1-1, 83 First St., Lot 54, 65 (NYR 189), 1958-1960; 1971 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 2-1-1, 89 First St., Lot 57 (NYR 189), 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 2-4-4, 11 Front St., Lot 15 (NYR 189), 1970; 1971-1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 2-4-4, 13-15 Front St., Lot 16-17 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 17-25 and 27-29 Front Street, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - 17-25 and 27-29 Front Street, Xerox Photos, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - 2-4-3, 31-41 Front St., Lot 13 (NYR 189), 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - 2-4-5, 32-36 Front St., Lot 8 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - 3-1-9, 43-53 Front St., Lot 16 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 3-1-13, 50-62 Front St., Lot 3-8 (NYR 189), 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - 3-1-9, 55 Front St., Lot 15 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 3-1-9, 57-61 Front St., Lot 14 (NYR 189), 1968; 1970-1976; Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Block 3-1-9, Lot 14, 57-61 Front St., Jean Frankel, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - 3-1-10, 63 Front St., Lot 261/2 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970; 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - 3-1-14, 64-66 Front Lot 1 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - 3-1-10, 65-83 Front Street, Lot 18-26 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1977 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - 3-1-10, 85-87 Front St., Lot 17 (NYR 189), 1971-1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Block 3-1-10, Lot 17, 85-87 Front Street (NYR 189), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Block 3-1-11 Parcel 28, 89 Front St., Max Levinson (NYR 189), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - 3-1-11, 89 Front St., Lot 28 (NYR 189), 1972-1975 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 3-1-11, 91 Front St., Lot 27 (NYR 189), 1947; 1954; 1966; 1970 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 3-1-11, 93 Front St., Lot 26 (NYR 189), 1966; 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 3-1-11, 99-107 Front St., Lot 21-23 (NYR 189), 1971; 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 3-1-11, 109 Front St., Lot 20 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Block 3-1-15, Parcels 8-11, 110-118 Front Street (NYR 189), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - 110-134 Front St., Corresp, Deeds, Title Rpt. (NYR 189), 1947; 1973 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - 110-134 Front St., Condemnation (NYR 189), 1973-1977 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - 110-134 Front St., Appraisals (NYR 189), 1966; 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - 3-1-11, 111-115 Front St., Lot 17-19 (NYR 189), 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 3-1-12, 117-125, Front St., Lot 16 (NYR 189), 1954; 1970-1974; 1975 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Edward Toback Block 3-1-12 Parcel 16 117-125 Front St, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Block 3-1-16, Parcels 1-9, 120-134 Front Street (NYR 189), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - 3-1-12, 127-133 Front St., Lot 15, 17-18 (NYR 189), 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - 3-1-12, 135-139 Front St., Lot 14 (NYR 189), 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 135-139 Front Street, Maurice Travers, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - 3-1-16, 136-140, Lot 10, Front Street (NYR 189), 1956; 1970; 1975 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - 2-1-1, 54-60 Grand St., Lot 13A (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - 2-1-1, Grand St., Back Lot 12A (NYR 189), 1971-1974; 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 2-1-1, 64 Grand St., Lot 11 (NYR 189), 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 2-1-1, 66 Grand St., Lot 10 (NYR 189), 1947; 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 2-1-1, 68 Grand St., Lot 9 (NYR 189), 1951; 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 2-1-1, 70 Grand St., Lot 8 (NYR 189), 1962-1963; 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 2-1-1, 70A Grand St., Lot 7 (NYR 189), 1962; 1968; 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 2-1-1, 72 Grand St., Lot 6 (NYR 189), 1963; 1966; 1971 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 2-1-1, 74 Grand St., Lot 5 (NYR 189), 1963; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 2-1-1, 76 Grand St., Lot 4 (NYR 189), 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 2-1-1, 78-80 Grand St., Lot 3 (NYR 189), 1959; 1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 2-1-1, 82-84 Grand St., Lot 2 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 2-1-1, 86 Grand St., Lot 1 (NYR 189), 1968; 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 2-5-5, 96 Grand St., Lot 11 (NYR 189), 1966; 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Block 2-5-5, Parcel 11, 96 Grand Street, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Parcel 2-5-5, Lot 11, 96 Grand Street, formerly Roskoski, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Parcel 2-5-5, 98 Grand, Board of Education Building, E. Newburgh R-189, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - 2-5-5, 104-106 Grand St., Lot 7 (NYR 189), 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 2-5-5, 108 Grand St., Lot 6 (NYR 189), 1959; 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 2-5-5, 110 Grand St., Lot 5 (NYR 189), 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 2-5-5, 110 Grand St., Lot 5 (NYR 189), 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 2-5-5, 112 Grand St., Lot 4 (NYR 189), 1952; 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 2-5-5, 114 Grand St., Lot 3 (NYR 189), 1959; 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 2-5-5, 116 Grand St., Lot 2 (NYR 189), 1946; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 2-5-5, 118 Grand St., Lot 1-23 (NYR 189), 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 3-2-4, 120-122 Grand St., Lot 1 (NYR 189), 1970; Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 3-2-4, Palatine Hotel 124-132 Grand St., Lot 2, 16-17 (NYR 189), 1962; 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - 3-2-5, 134-150 Grand St., Lot 1-2 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Block 3-2-5, Parcels 1 and 2, 140-150 Grand Street, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - 140-150 Grand St., Dutch Reformed Church Property (NYR 189), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Block 3-2-5, Parcels 1 and 2, 140-150 Grand Street (NYR 189), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 3-2-5, 152 Grand St., Lot 3 (NYR 189), 1955; 1966 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 3-2-5, 170 Grand St., Lot 10 (NYR 189), 1955; 1966 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 3-2-5, 180-184 Grand St., Lot 141/2-15 (NYR 189), 1957; 1966 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 3-2-5, 186-192 Grand St., Lot 16A (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 4-5-2, 208 Grand St., Lot 1 (NYR 189), 1964-1970; Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 4-5-2, 210 Grand St., Lot 2-3 (NYR 189), 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 4-5-2, 214-216 Grand St., Lot 4-5 (NYR 189), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 4-5-2, 218 Grand St., Lot 6 (NYR 189), 1966; 1971; Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 4-5-2, 220 Grand St., Lot 7 (NYR 189), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 4-5-2, 222-26 Grand St., Lot 8-9 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 4-5-2, 228 Grand St., Lot 10 (NYR 189), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 4-5-2, 228A Grand St., Lot 11 (NYR 189), 1963 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 4-5-2, 230-32 Grand St., Lot 12-13 (NYR 189), 1970-1971; Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 4-5-2, 234 Grand St., Lot 14 (NYR 189), 1970-1971; Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 4-5-2, 236 Grand St., Lot 15 (NYR 189), 1970-1971; Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 4-5-2, 244 Grand St., Lot 18 (NYR 189), 1968; 1970 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 4-5-2, 250 Grand St., Lot 20 (NYR 189), 1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 4-6-2, 278 Grand St., Lot 5 (NYR 189), 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 4-6-2, 280 Grand St., Lot 6 (NYR 189), 1966-1972; Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 4-6-2, 282 Grand St., Lot 7 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - 4-6-2, 284 Grand St., Lot 8 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 4-6-2, 286 Grand St., Lot 9 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - 4-6-2, 288-294 Grand St., Lot 10-13 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - 4-6-2, 296-298 Grand St., Lot 14 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Block 4-6-2, Parcel 14, 296-298 Grand Street, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - 296-298 Grand Street, Carl Wallace Jr. and Helen Wallace, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - 4-6-2, 300 Grand St., Lot 15 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - 4-6-2, 302 Grand St., Lot 16-16A (NYR 189), 1966; 1971 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - 4-6-2, 304-308 Grand St., Lot 17-19 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - 4-6-2, 310-3k2 Grand St., Lot 20-21 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 4-6-2, 314 Grand St., Lot 22 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 4-6-2, 318 Grand St., Lot 24 (NYR 189), 1967 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 2-1-2, 1-5 High St., Lot 1,2,3 (NYR 189), 1953; 1968; 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 2-1-1, 2 High Street, Lot 52 (NYR 189), 1970-1975; 1987 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - 2-1-1, 4 High St., Lot 51 (NYR 189), 1946; 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 2-1-1, 6 High St., Lot 50 (NYR 189), 1958; 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 2-1-2, 7-11 High St., Lot 4-5 (NYR 189), 1956; 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 2-1-1, 8 High St., Lot 49 (NYR 189), 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 2-1-1, 10 High St., Lot 48 (NYR 189), 1953; 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 2-1-1, 12-24 High St., Lot 42-47 (NYR 189), 1950; 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 2-1-2, 13 High St., Lot 6 (NYR 189), 1956; 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 2-1-2, 15 High St., Lot 7 (NYR 189), 1966; 1972-1977 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 2-1-2, 17 High St., Lot 8 (NYR 189), 1962; 1966; 1971 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Block 2-1-1, Parcel 49, 8 High Street, Florence DeLong, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - 2-1-2, 19 High St., Lot 9 (NYR 189), 1955; 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Block 2-1-2, 21 High Street, Parcel 10, Edward Bizzell, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - 2-1-2, 21 High St., Lot 10, Frances L. Bizzell (NYR 189), 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - 2-1-2, 23 High St., Lot 11 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - 2-1-2, 25 High St., Lot 12 (NYR 189), 1963; 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - 2-1-2, 27 High St., Lot 13 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - 2-1-2, 29 High St., Lot 14 (NYR 189), 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - 2-1-2, 31 High St., Lot 15 (NYR 189), 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - 2-1-2, 33-35 High St., Lot 16 (NYR 189), 1957; 1970-1975 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 2-1-2, 37-41 High St., Lot 17-19 (NYR 189), 1966; 1971-1975; 1977 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 2-1-2, 43 High St., Lot 20 (NYR 189), 1956; 1963; 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 2-1-2, 45 High St., Lot 21 (NYR 189), 1962; 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Block 2-1-2, 47-49 High St., Parcels 22 and 23, Jean Frankel, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - 2-1-2, 51 High St., Lot 24 (NYR 189), 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - 2-1-2, 53-57 High St. and 46-52 Broadway, Lot 25-28A (NYR 189), 1945; 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - 2-4-1 High Street, Lot 15 (NYR 189), 1966; 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 2-4-1, High St., Lot 16 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 4-3-2, 2-16 Hudson Street Lot 36-43 (NYR 189), 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 68 Lake Street, Bard Chevrolet, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Parcel 6, 92-104 Lake Street (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Parcel 6, 92-104 Lake Street (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - NDP NY A-10, Lake Street, Parcel 9 Rockwell Vending Co., 1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Reuse Appraisal Lake St., Parcels 1, 2, 3, + 4, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Reuse Appraisal Lake St., Parcels 1, 2, 3, + 4, w/ review, 1967-1970 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parcel No. 5, Lac Pac Realty Corp., 1973 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Lake Street Urban Renewal Area Parcels 6-15 and Industrial 2, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - NDP NYA-10, Lake Street, Parcel 8, Larkin Ice and Cold Storage Corporation, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Appraisal Report and Valuation Analysis Lake Street Parcel 3, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parcel 15, Marion E. Donahue, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Reuse Appraisal Disposition Parcel Number 16, Lake Street Project, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parcel No. 16, Brad Chevrolet Inc., 1972 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parcel 17, Nick and Rosalie Rascino, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parce1 18, Mathew and Katherine Kehoe, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parcel 19, Nicola and Isabel Mancini, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parcel 20, Theresa Hayden and Mattin, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - NDP N.Y. A-10 (Lake Street) Parcel 20, Theresa Hayden and Mattin D., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Project NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Project Parcel No. 21, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parcel 24 Herman and Florence Zaransky, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parcel 25, Michael Stein, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Lake Street Parcel 26 NYA-10, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parcel 26, Herman Zaransky & Luke Stein, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parcel 27, Highland Provision Co. Inc., 1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parcel No. 28, John T. Conway, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parcel No. 29, Howard Boice, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parcel 30, Vermont Terminal Corporation, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - NDP NYA-10 Lake Street Parcel 31, Joseph and Amanda Rizzo, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - 2-4-1, 20-22 Montgomery Street, Lot 7 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - 2-4-1, 6-8 Montgomery St., Lot 13 (NYR 189), 1962-1964; 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 2-4-1, 4 Montgomery St., Lot 14 (NYR 189), 1966; 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - 2-4-1, 10 Montgomery St., Lot 12 (NYR 189), 1955; 1972 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 2-4-1, 12 Montgomery St., Lot 11 (NYR 189), 1952; 1970-1972; 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 2-4-1, 14 Montgomery St., Lot 10 (NYR 189), 1955; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 2-4-1, 16 Montgomery St., Lot 9 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 2-4-1, 18 Montgomery St., Lot 8 (NYR 189), 1947; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 2-5-5, 21 Montgomery St., Lot 25 (NYR 189), 1960; 1966; 1970-1974 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 2-5-5, 23 Montgomery St., Lot 26 (NYR 189), 1966; 1971 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - 2-4-1, 24 Montgomery St., Lot 6 (NYR 189), 1964; 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 2-5-5, 25 Montgomery St., Lot 27 (NYR 189), 1952; 1966; 1970 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - 2-4-1, 26 Montgomery St., Lot 5 (NYR 189), 1957; 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 2-5-5, 27-33 Montgomery St., Lot 28&29 (NYR 189), 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - 28-30 Montgomery Street, Jean Frankel, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - 2-4-1, 32 Montgomery St., Lot 2 (NYR 189), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 2-4-1, 34-42 Montgomery St., Lot 1 (NYR 189), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 2-5-5, 35 Montgomery St., Lot 30 (NYR 189), 1971-1974; Undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - 2-5-5, 37 Montgomery St., Lot 31 (NYR 189), 1971-1975 (Box 9, Folder 26)